clozette.co 2014-05-30

# Clozette | Your Personal Online Closet and Fashion Social Network

Privacy Policy  
---  
  
This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by Clozette Pte Ltd and its subsidiary and associated companies (collectively, " **Clozette** ") under **Clause 1** below.

For the purpose of this Policy, " **we** " and " **our** " shall refer to Clozette.  

**1\. When is Information Collected from You?**

  1. When you register as a member or use any of our services on websites owned and/or operated by us, hosted by us on behalf of our business partners or use services on such websites (collectively, "the Site")  

  2. When you take part in any contest, survey or promotion conducted by us and/or our business partners.  

  3. When you make purchases or elect to receive email and/or text messages about upcoming events or promotions. When you choose to use these additional features, we require you to provide additional personal information such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information, and we may request additional personal information such as your shopping preferences and demographics.  

  | 

  1. The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on the Site;
  2. The number of unique visitors to the Site;  

  3. How long these unique visitors (on average) spend on the Site when they do visit; and
  4. Common entry and exit points into the Site.
  5. This information is collated by the Third Party Market Research Company and provided to Clozette to assist in analyzing the usage of the Site.
  6. Pages on the Site may be coded with software which enables the Third Party Market Research Company and Clozette to track visitors to the Site.

**2\. What is the Information Used For?**

  1. Information which you provide to us may be used and disclosed by us and our affiliates, business partners and contractors (who may be based outside Singapore) for the following purposes: 

    1. to respond to your requests and queries;
    2. to provide goods and services to you;
    3. to verify and process your personal particulars and payments;
    4. to communicate with you;
    5. to enforce contractual and legal rights and obligations;
    6. for marketing research, user profile and statistical analysis;
    7. to send you information, promotions, updates, and marketing and advertising materials in relation to our goods and services and those of third party organizations;
    8. complying with law, the requests of law enforcement and regulatory officials, or orders of court; and
    9. for any other purposes for which we have obtained your consent, including during the registration process under our Terms of Use Agreement.

  2. In the event that you participate in contests or other promotional programs on the Site sponsored or organized by third parties or purchase goods and services offered by third parties or offer goods and services to third parties on the Site, your information may be disclosed to and used by such third parties.  

**3\. Use of Cookies**

  1. Clozette uses "cookies", where a small data file is sent to your browser to store and track information about you when you enter the Site. The cookie is used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their preferred sites.

  2. Like many web site operators, Clozette may use an independent company (the " **Third Party Market Research Company** ") to measure and analyse the Internet usage across the Site. Clozette uses the Third Party Market Research Company's services to collect the following core information on the usage of the Site, including:

    1. The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on the Site;

    2. The number of unique visitors to the Site; 

    3. How long these unique visitors (on average) spend on the Site when they do visit; and

    4. Common entry and exit points into the Site. 

  3. This information is collated by the Third Party Market Research Company and provided to Clozette to assist in analyzing the usage of the Site. 
  4. Pages on the Site may be coded with software which enables the Third Party Market Research Company and Clozette to track visitors to the Site. 

**4\. How Do We Protect Your Information**

  1. We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

  2. The Site encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your PC to our servers. In addition, only those employees and third parties who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access.

**5\. Privacy Policy Changes**

  1. We may, from time to time, change our Privacy Policy for the Site. We will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

**If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at[info@clozette.co.](mailto:info@clozette.co)**
